Here we have an athlete preparing for a game.
这里，我们看到一位运动员正在为比赛做准备。
They've put on their gear and done their warmup, and now it's time for one more routine— stretching.
他已经穿戴好装备，完成了热身，现在还要进行最后一个固定环节，那就是拉伸。
Typically, athletes stretch before physical activity to avoid injuries like muscle strains and tears.
通常，运动员会在运动前进行拉伸，以避免肌肉拉伤、撕裂等损伤。
But does stretching actually prevent these issues?
但拉伸真的能预防这些问题吗？
And if so, how long do the benefits of stretching last?
如果可以，那么拉伸带来的益处能持续多久呢？
To answer these questions, we need to know what's actually happening in the body when we stretch.
要回答这些问题，我们需要了解拉伸时身体里究竟发生了什么。
There are two kinds of stretching our athlete might be doing.
这位运动员可能会做两种类型的拉伸。
Dynamic stretches, which are controlled movements that engage a range of muscles throughout the motion.
第一种是动态拉伸，它是指受控制的动作，在整个动作过程中会调动多组肌肉。
And static stretches, where the stretcher holds a position to keep specific muscles at a fixed length and tension.
第二种是静态拉伸，即保持一个姿势，使特定肌肉维持在固定的长度和张力下。
Our athlete is currently doing a static hamstring stretch— a 30 second interval where he pulls his hamstring beyond its usual range of motion.
此时，这位运动员正在做一次30秒的静态腿后肌拉伸，把腿后肌拉伸到超过平时活动范围的位置。
However, while we often think of stretching a muscle like stretching a rubber band, muscles are actually comprised of various tissue types, which interact to make a complex material.
然而，虽然我们常把拉伸肌肉比作拉橡皮筋，但肌肉实际上由多种不同类型的组织构成，这些组织相互作用，形成一种复杂的材料。
Rubber is elastic, meaning it resists being stretched and then returns to its original shape.
橡胶具有弹性，也就是说，它会抵抗拉伸，并最终恢复原来的形状。
But muscle is viscoelastic.
但肌肉属于黏弹性材料。
This means that, in addition to those elastic qualities, muscle changes under the stress of being stretched.
这意味着，除了具有弹性之外，肌肉在受到拉伸应力时本身也会发生变化。
Let's see this in action.
让我们看看这一过程是如何实际发生的。
At the large scale, this hamstring stretch is pulling on layers of protective tissue surrounding the muscle fibers, as well as the tendons that connect this muscle to nearby bones.
从宏观层面来看，这次腿后肌拉伸会牵拉包裹肌纤维的多层保护组织，以及连接肌肉和附近骨骼的肌腱。
These tissues contain elastic proteins like collagen and elastin, which allow them to slightly elongate over the duration of the stretch.
这些组织中含有胶原蛋白和弹性蛋白等弹性蛋白质，使它们能够在拉伸过程中略微延长。
At the smaller scale, these skeletal muscle fibers are comprised of millions of sarcomeres— the smallest contracting unit of muscle tissue.
从更微观的层面来看，这些骨骼肌纤维由数百万个肌小节组成，而肌小节是肌肉组织最小的收缩单位。
Sarcomere's long, fibrous proteins can relax to elongate muscle fibers or they can contract to shorten them— pulling on tendons and protective tissue to create the force propelling our athlete's body.
肌小节中细长的纤维蛋白可以放松，使肌纤维变长；也可以收缩，使肌纤维缩短，从而牵拉肌腱和保护组织，产生推动运动员身体运动的力量。
And when those tissues have been stretched out, they retain their strength at longer lengths, allowing our athlete to take full advantage of his improved range of motion.
当这些组织被拉长后，它们能够在更长的长度下保持力量，从而使运动员能够充分利用自己增加的活动范围。
Unlike a rubber band, this muscle's resistance to stretching decreases with each 30 second stretch, allowing our athlete to continually elongate his hamstring.
与橡皮筋不同，肌肉对拉伸的阻力会随着每一次30秒的拉伸而减小，因此运动员可以不断把腿后肌拉得更长。
And this improved flexibility likely decreases the chance of incurring certain muscle injuries.
这种柔韧性的提升，很可能会降低发生某些肌肉损伤的风险。
But due to muscle's elastic properties, this effect will be gone in just 10 minutes without further activity.
但由于肌肉具有弹性，这种效果如果没有进一步活动，仅仅10分钟后就会消失。
The exercise from his match should elevate his muscle's temperature and continue elongating the muscle, maintaining his increased flexibility throughout the game.
比赛中的运动会提高肌肉温度，并持续拉长肌肉，从而使增加的柔韧性在整场比赛中得以维持。
But once he gives his hamstrings a break, they'll retract back to their previous state.
但一旦腿后肌得到休息，它们就会回缩到之前的状态。
So if all this is just temporary, how can you permanently improve your flexibility?
那么，如果这一切都只是暂时的，又怎样才能永久提高柔韧性呢？
For skeletal muscles, improved flexibility comes from additional sarcomeres, which allow you to maintain strength at even greater lengths.
对于骨骼肌来说，柔韧性的提升来自于新增的肌小节，它们使你能够在更长的肌肉长度下仍然保持力量。
Sarcomeres are added and subtracted to muscles depending on how frequently they're used, so improving overall flexibility requires a comprehensive stretching regimen.
肌小节会根据肌肉使用的频率不断增加或减少，因此，提高整体柔韧性需要一套系统、全面的拉伸计划。
Plus, you need to stretch often— very often.
此外，你需要经常拉伸，而且是非常经常。
Current research suggests at least 10 minutes a day for roughly two months.
目前的研究建议，每天至少拉伸10分钟，坚持大约两个月。
And since it's unsafe to hold any stretch for too long, it's recommended that you break up your stretching within any given session.
由于长时间保持任何一种拉伸姿势都不安全，因此建议在每一次训练中把拉伸时间分成多个小段进行。
Frequent stretching also makes lasting changes to your brain.
频繁拉伸还会对你的大脑产生持久性的改变。
The more you stretch a muscle, the higher your pain threshold becomes, allowing you to stretch further and further.
你拉伸肌肉越多，你的疼痛耐受阈值就会越高，从而使你能够拉得越来越远。
Long-term improvements to your flexibility can provide a better range of motion for your joints, potentially reducing your risk of muscle injury in the short and long-term.
柔韧性的长期提升能够让关节拥有更大的活动范围，并有可能降低你在短期和长期发生肌肉损伤的风险。
But it's also possible to stretch too much, as flexible people can move their joints in potentially dangerous ways.
不过，拉伸也可能过度，因为柔韧性很好的人可能会让关节活动到存在危险的角度。
Stretching also isn't helpful for every kind of movement, especially those where muscle injuries aren't very common.
拉伸也并非对所有运动都有帮助，尤其是那些本身肌肉损伤并不常见的运动。
For example, long distance running only involves a small range of motion for the joints involved, so stretching is unlikely to prevent that sport's most common injuries.
例如，长跑涉及的关节活动范围本来就比较小，因此拉伸不太可能预防这项运动中最常见的损伤。
When it comes down to it, different lifestyles require different kinds of mobility.
归根结底，不同的生活方式需要不同类型的身体活动能力。
And no single stretching regimen is flexible enough to fit every situation.
没有任何一种拉伸方案能够适用于所有情况。